import { v4 as uuid } from "uuid";

export const Questions = [
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "Which is the smallest ocean in the world?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Pacific"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Atlantic"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Arctic"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Indian"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Arctic",
        quizCat: "World Quiz"
    },

    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "Dead sea is located between which two countries?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Jordan and Sudan"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Jordan and Israel"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Turkey and UAE"},
            {id: 4, opt: "UAE and Egypt"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Jordan and Israel",
        quizCat: "World Quiz"
    },

    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "Which country is known as the 'Playground of Europe?'",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Germany"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Italy"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Austria"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Switzerland"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Switzerland",
        quizCat: "World Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?'",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Asia"},
            {id: 2, opt: "North America"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Africa"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Europe"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Africa",
        quizCat: "World Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "In which country white elephant is found?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Thailand"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Indonesia"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Sri Lanka"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Vietnam"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Thailand",
        quizCat: "World Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "The Versatile Bollywood actor Irrfan Khan, who recently passed away, had won National award for which movie?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Lunch Box"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Paan Singh Tomar"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Life of Pi"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Haidar"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Paan Singh Tomar",
        quizCat: "Bollywood Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "Which Following Ambris Puri Film Features the Iconic dialogue 'Mogambo Khush Hua'?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Mr. India"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Damini"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Diljale"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Badshah"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Mr. India",
        quizCat: "Bollywood Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "Which horror movie is based on mythology?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Haunted"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Pizza"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Tumbbad"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Ek Thi Dayan"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Tumbbad",
        quizCat: "Bollywood Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "In film “zindagi na milengi dobara” , where did Three Friends Meet ?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "America"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Mumbai"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Spain"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Italy"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Spain",
        quizCat: "Bollywood Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "Which is not a Ranbir Kapoor Movie?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Rockstar"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Barfi"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Tamasha"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Gunday"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Gunday",
        quizCat: "Bollywood Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "How did Shivaji Maharaj escaped from Aurangzeb's Prison?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Through tunnel"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Hiding in Box"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Through exchange clothes"},
            {id: 4, opt: "by fighting"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Hiding in Box",
        quizCat: "History Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "To which king belongs the Lion capital at Sarnath?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Chandragupta"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Ashoka"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Kanishka"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Harsha"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Ashoka",
        quizCat: "History Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "The language of discourses of Gautama Buddha was",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Bhojpuri"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Magadhi"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Pali"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Sanskrit"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Pali",
        quizCat: "History Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "Tulsidas, the author of Ramcharitmanas, was a contemporary of which of the following rulers?",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "Akbar"},
            {id: 2, opt: "Humayun"},
            {id: 3, opt: "Shahjahan"},
            {id: 4, opt: "Sher Shah Suri"}
        ],
        correctAns: "Akbar",
        quizCat: "History Quiz"
    },
    {
        id: uuid(),
        question: "The Upanishads are",
        options: [
            {id: 1, opt: "a source of Hindu philosophy"},
            {id: 2, opt: "books of ancient Hindu laws"},
            {id: 3, opt: "books on social behavior of man"},
            {id: 4, opt: "prayers to God"}
        ],
        correctAns: "a source of Hindu philosophy",
        quizCat: "History Quiz"
    },
]